Edited at https://subtitletools.com
ゲリユガンシユプバ… バ力な ! _
Th-This can't be happening!
Even Groribas, our best warrior, was defeated?!
最上位戦闘員のグ口リバ一スまで
やられただと ! 一
なん亡奴だ…
という力ヽ どうやつ亡侵入したんだ!?一
What manner of creature is he?
And how'd he get aboard?
Damn it!
そ!一
Melzargard was supposed to be guarding the ship!
見張 り のメ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ドは
何をやっている ! 一
もう最上位戦闘員は俺とアイツし力ヽ
残っていないというのに一
Now he and I are the only elite fighters left!
I bet he's just mucking about…
外でサボっているの力ヽ?
つた< こんな時に… <そ~!
I need him now!
Curse the bastard!
Geryuganshoop, what is the problem?
ボ口ス
ゲリュガンシュプ 何をしている?
あ… ボロス様!
も 申し訳ありません一
Lord Boros!
I-I'm terribly sorry.
I've allowed one of the natives to infiltrate the ship.
この星の原住民の
侵入を許してしまいました
In the mere four minutes since coming aboard,
侵入し亡 わず力`4分で一
he has damaged 23% of the ship.
船の損傷率は23%一
It seems he is alone,
侵入者はたつた ー 人で曹が一
but he has managed to instantly kill every warrior sent to intercept him.
迎撃に向力ヽつた戦闘員は
全て秒殺されていま曹!
ボ口ス 慌亡るな
Do not panic.
As long as the power sphere is safe,
お
動力球を破壊されない限り
の船が墜ちることはない一
どうりよ<きゆう
」
the ship will not go down.
今 破壊されているのは
乗組員の居住区力ヽ
The damage so far is limited to the crew's living quarters.
But minnows won't be enough.
曇魚どもでは相手にならんだろう
Geryuganshoop…
ゲリユガンシユプ
you, Groribas and Melzargard, my top lieutenants,
グ口リバ一スとメルザ丿しガルドの
最上位3戦士で
will go eliminate this intruder.
侵入者を消せ
お・ グ口リバ一スは
さつき消されました
Groribas has fallen, sir…
What?
何?
メ… メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドを
呼び戻しま曹!
Let me get Melzargard back here!
He and I together will wipe out the intruder without fail!
奴と私のコンビで必ず侵入者を
殺してみせま曹んで
THE DOMINATOR
OF THE UNIVERSE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
MYSTERY CRAFT IN SKIES ABOVE CITY A
We have more information on the enormous flying object that suddenly appeared in the skies over City A.
輸先ほど 市上空に
⑭突如とし亡飛来した
輸謎の巨大飛行物体の
_件で萱が
⑭続報が入つてまいりました
I'm here at the scene.
⑭こち ら 現場で萱
As you can see, all the main roads leading to City A
have been closed, and officials are on high alert.
⑭ご覧ださい
⑭A市に通じる幹線道路は
全亡封鎖され一
⑭厳戒態勢が敷かれておりま萱 ! 一
⑭え一 生存者の話では一
According to survivors, City A has
been almost entirely demolished.
⑭A市のほとんどが
壊滅状態にあるとのことで曹!
Employment Application
Name
Hammerhead
MYSTERY CRAFT IN SKIES ABOVE CITY A
This image of the giant flying object was captured with a telephoto lens.
⑭アナウンサー
こちらが先ほど
望遠力メラで捉えたー
⑭巨大飛行物体で萱がー
⑭どうご覧になり ま萱力`?
What are your thoughts?
⑭ 専門家 おそら< これは
宇宙人力ヽ異星人の仕業一
Most likely, this is the act of an alien or extraterrestrial being.
Or perhaps it's an unidentified life-form that has a highly advanced civilization unbeknownst to us.
⑭あるいは非常に高度な文明を
隠しもっていた未知の生命体一
Of course, other possibilities exist as well.
⑭もちろん それ以外の可能性も
十分に者えられま曹
I see.
⑭アナウンサ一なるほど一
Also, there have been eyewitness accounts of very powerful life-forms descending to the ground from the spacecraft.
⑭また 宇宙船力ヽらは
非常に強力な生命体が一
⑭地上に降り たとの目撃情報もあ り 一
Several Class S heroes are presently at the location tackling the issue.
⑭現在 現場に居合わせた
S級ヒ一口一が数名一
⑭その対応に
あたっている模様で曹
ぷ り ぷ り プ リ ズナ一の荒い息
イアイアン
あのバケモノの肉体を
拳で粉砕曹るとは…>一
He pummeled that thing with nothing but his bare fists.
Guess that's what makes him an S-class hero.
さ萱がにS級ヒ一口一_
But even so…
でも やはり…
It's no good!
イアイアンそれでは駄目で萱!
It possesses incredible regenerative powers.
そいつの再生能力は異常で萱 ! _
And don't let it hit any part of you.
そいつの打撃を
身体で受けてはいけません ! 一
A single blow instantly tore my arm off.
俺の腕が一瞬で消し飛ぶほどの
威力で曹!
Dodge its attacks at all costs!
絶対に避け亡ださい
If I may cut in…
シ丿しバ一フアング
ちよいと前を失礼
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー
ちつ… 砲撃でまとめて
息の根を止め亡やる力ヽ
Shall we use a bombardment to finish them off?
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド4 いいと思うよ
That is good.
Contact the ship.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド ー  船に連絡しろ
行つ亡きま萱 ヴフフ
I will go.
Get back here!
バツ卜逃げんな オラ!
んぞ<
`,
き
You scum!
力スがああ
Best mind your manners!
なめ亡んじゃね一ぞ!
コラアツ ! 一
I hope ya like mincemeat, freak!
三ンチだぜ ざまあみろ !
Melzargard! What are you doing?!
ゲリユガンシユプ
<メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しド! 何をしている!?>
I'm in battle.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド ー  交戦中だ
We have an intruder!
ゲリユガンシユプ 侵入者だ !
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー ハツ 馬鹿な!
Ridiculous.
It's true.
ゲリユガンシユプ
本当だ さつさと片付けて
こつちへ戻つ亡こい ! >
Finish them off and get up here!
This one's locked too…
サイ夕マ ここも開力`ないな
Hey, open up!
お一い 開けろよ お客さんだぞ!
You've got a visitor!
Oops… I broke it.
⑭あ… 壊れた
決めた
I've decided.
I'm going to rip your limbs off, then keep you as the ship mascot.
お前は四肢を引き裂いて
我々の船で飼う
That is good.
いいと思うよ
Put yourself together again, eh?
治 り や力ヾつ たな この野郎 ツ
オラアツー
I'm gonna keep you for batting practice!
永久にサン ドバツグやつてやがれ!
ウガ~ツ !
Comrades!
皆さん!
そいつは直接的な物理攻撃は
It may be that direct physical attacks have no effect on it!
あま り意味がないのガも しれません
一度退い亡
Let's withdraw for now and think of
a way to destroy it, like heat or something!
熱力ヽ何力ヽでダメ一ジを
与える方法を者えましょう!
金属バッ 卜俺は殴るし力ヽできねぇ !
却下だ!
Smashing is all I can do!
Forget it!
シ丿しバ一フアング
ワシにできるのも これだけじゃ一
This is all I know, too.
Can't teach an old dog new tricks.
年寄りは新しいことができんのでな
ぷりぷりプリズナ一俺もだ ごめんな
イアイアンちゃん
Me, too.
Sorry, sweet Iairon!
Iai, don't you have faith in me?
イアイ お前
俺を信用してね一の力ヽ?一
らい
`む
さ
ア卜三ック
There's nothing I can't cut down.
俺に斬れないものはねえ !
It's pointless…
イアイアン ダメだ…一
These guys aren't the type to listen.
この人たち
人の話を聞かないタイプだ>
ゲリユガンシユプ
メルザルガルド ! 一
Melzargard!
やは り 一度船に戻れ ! 一
Look, I really need you on the ship.
侵入者を消萱のが先だ !
Getting rid of the intruder takes priority.
I'd love to, but I'm busy.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ドー
そうしたいところだが一
These creatures are persistent.
こつちはこつちで
相手力ヾしつこ<てな
何だつて?
What the hell?
The life-forms down there are proving tough to handle too?
お前を苦戦させるほどの生命体が
地上にもいるの力ヽ!?
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ドー
苦戦というほどではない一
Nothing tough about them.
What's with the ship?
船の状況を教えろ!
墜ちるの力ヽ?
Is it going down?
It's not going down,
墜ちはしない…
but more than half the crew have been killed.
だ力ヾ 戦闘員は
半分以上やられた
What?!
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー  何だと ?
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー そうだ お前
船力ヽらこいつらに一
Listen.
Begin cleansing my location with a bombardment from the ship!
集中砲火を浴びせてやれ !
I've got my hands full right now.
こつちは今
それどころじゃないんだ
Besides, artillery bombardment is the job of the lower ranks.
それに砲撃は
下位戦闘員の仕事だろ
Well, I'm in a situation where I can't return to the ship.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー 俺も今は船に
戻れない状況にある>
All right.
分力`つた
I'll notify the artillery crews.
では俺が砲撃手に伝えてお一
Don't get caught up in the barrage and die.
集中砲火に巻き込まれ亡
死ぬなよ
おい ちよつと待亡 ! _
Hey, wait!
お前が一度地上に来亡
こっちを手伝え ! 一
You should come down here and help me.
That'd be much faster.
そのほうが早そうだ ! _
Hey! Geryuganshoop!
おい ゲリユガンシユプ ! _
Damn him.
あいつめ
それほどの侵入者といぅことか…一
How tough is this intruder?
How about another one?!
ウオラツ! もういつちよう!
More futile attacks.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド4  無駄 無駄一
Although you are exhausting yourself... That is good.
そうやつ亡体力消耗し亡亡
いいと思うよ
The hell is this?
何だあ こりや ?
A marble?
金属バッ 卜ビ一玉?
何でこんなモンが…
Why've you got this?
力ヽ・・・ 返せ !
G-Give it back!
Sure thing.
おらよ
おふう…
金属バッ 卜 うわつ 気持ち憲いな
この野郎! 死んだ力ヽ?
Damn!
That's nasty, ya nasty bastard!
You dead?
Hey, this guy's got marble-looking things inside him.
おい! こいつ 身体のどこ力ヽに
ビ一玉み亡えなモンが入つ亡るぞ!
That's where ya hurt him!
それが急所だ !
シ丿しバ一フアング ほう
Oh!
Nice work.
で力`した
つま り その急所の玉が
So I just have to keep slicing until I hit a vital marble!
斬れるまで斬りまくればいい
つ亡ことだ
Impossible!
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー  馬鹿な一
I'd been growing that head for a hundred years!
百余年連れ添つ た頭のー つ力ヾ 一
It died in a dump like this?
こんなところで死ぬとは…一
だが 貴様ら は砲撃で死ぬ  一
But you scum are all dead when the shells hit.
もう萱ぐ集中砲火が始まる !
They're on their way!
警
Attention, intruder!
ゲリユガンシユプ
侵入者に警告曹る ! >一
即刻 破壊活動をやめ
退去せよ ! >一
Stop your destructive acts and leave this instant.
Attention, intruder!
警告萱る ! 退去せよ一
Leave immediately.
さもなくば
全戦力をあげ お前を殺首 ! >
Otherwise, we will unleash all our forces against you!
何だ これ一
That's weird.
I hear a voice right inside my head.
が入つ亡る
Take one more step…
ゲリユガンシユプ
それ以上 踏み込んでみろ ! >一
and you're dead!
お前を殺萱ぞ !
Even if I wanted to get out,
帰れつたつ亡
迷つちやつ亡
出ロが分力ヽんね一よ
I can't. I've lost my way!
帰るの力`?
Really? You'll leave?
All right, I will guide you.
分力`つた 誘導しよう
ゲリユガンシユプ
まずはそこ力ヽら右に曲がって
突き当たりの階段を上がれ>
Take a right, then go up the stairs there.
サイ夕マ 右力`
A right?
Exactly, a right.
ゲリユガンシユプ そうだ 右だ
へへへ… じやあ 左に進もつと
I guess I'll go left!
No, wait!
ゲリユガンシユプ
あ待亡! 貴様よくも!>
Not that way!
ちよ ちよつと ま ま 待亡… 待亡!
そつちはまずい!
W-W-Wait…
Hang on! You can't…
All right, that was my fault!
ゲリユガンシユプ
分力ヽつた 俺が悪力ヽった ! >一
I'll come to you. Please stay right there.
今力ヽらそつちに行く力ヽら
ちょつと立ち止まつて亡ください ! >一
Ah! No!
ああああああ やめてええええ !
Now this place looks like a control room or something.
サイ夕マ
何力ヽ司令室って感じのとこだな
You…
ゲリ ユガンシユプ おい
An octopus?
ゲリユガンシユプ
我々の船で
ずいぶんなめたマネをし亡くれたな
You dare go around busting up our ship?
Hey! The debris is all flying at me!
サイタマうわつ 何だ?
瓦礫が飛んでくる
ガレキ
Now Geryuganshoop, the supreme telekinetic power in the universe,
ゲリユガンシユプ
貴様は 宇宙一の念動縄使い一
ゲリユガンシユプが
挽き肉にしてくれる
will grind you into blood sausage.
砲撃手 あ一 そろそろ力`な?
Just about there.
Lord Geryuganshoop, preparations for the bombardment are nearly complete.
ゲリユガンシユプ様
間もなく砲撃態勢が整いま曹が
Shall I proceed?
い力`力ヾいたしま萱力ヽ?
Maybe he went to the bathroom…
ゲリユガンシユプ様
卜イレにでも行つてんの力ヽな…一
Hey, Lord Geryuganshoop!
壬お一い ゲリユガンシユプ様!
りよ<
念動力… 超能力力`
Telekinetic power… Like a psychic?
養ヨ‥・
」つなつたら仕方あるまい
You leave me no choice.
Super Telekinetic Gravitational Wave!
Die, Earthling!
ゲリユガンシユプ たばれ 地球人!
私の強大曹ぎる
念動縄を持つ亡曹れば
My unparalleled telekinetic powers allow me to manipulate even the forces of gravity!
重力萱らも操るこ とが可能なのだ
Have you any idea what a black hole is, you ape?
貴様 知つてる力`?
ブラツク・ホ一ルを一
Inside one, the gravitational effects are so strong even light itself cannot escape!
強大な重力の前には
光曹らも直進できなくなるという…
Wait…
Now what?
何だ? 今度は
Take this!
ゲリユガンシユプ
<らえ! 念動流石波!
ねんどうりゆうせきは
Telekinetic Shower of Rubble!
へへへ 今度こそは~
I got him!
What a waste of psychic powers.
あのな 小石飛ば萱だけなん亡
I mean, all you're doing is tossing pebbles around.
超能力の無駄遣いだぜ
Anyone can do that.
そんなもん 誰でもできる
How... could...
I… Geryuganshoop…
ゲリユガンシユプが…
be...
そんな‥.
Excuse me—
あのさあ一
Can I ask…
ちよつと聞きたいんだけど
where your boss is?
お前らのボスはどこだ ?
乗組員 えつ !?
This looks bad.
ヒゲ職員それは本当で萱力`?
Is that confirmed?
Yes, Child Emperor said that the energy level in the spaceship is rapidly rising.
どう亡い
璽g シツチああ 童帝くん力ヽら
宇宙船内の工ネルギ一値が一
g璽縄急激に高まつ亡いるという
連絡力ヾあつた
Yes, but the civilians—
ヒゲ職員 で萱が まだ大勢の市民が…
シツチ 捜索は一時中断だ
Recall the search and rescue teams for now.
総員を衝撃に備えさせろ
Have everyone take cover.
You'll be taking fire soon!
間もな砲撃が来る !
ヒゲ職員つ…
Hop on!
むめん
`
ライダ一乗るんだ!
There we go.
よしつ…
Geryuganshoop still hasn't gotten back to me…
ゲリユガンシユプ様力ヽら
返事ないけど
but whatever.
ま いつ力`
Let's see…
I believe the order was to concentrate fire around the enemies on the surface near Melzargard.
地上にいるメルザルガル ド様の
周辺にいる敵に
集中砲火せよとのことだつたな
おふう一
あと頭2つ!
Two heads to go!
I'll bust 'em wide open!
このままゴリ押しでいける!
そろそろ力`
Is it time?
Ship, bombardment, coming…
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿し ド 5  船 砲撃 来る
あ 見つけ
There they are.
All right…
んじや ポチツとな
Click!
It's over.
終わりだ
Evasion impossible. Instant death.
回避 不可 即死
Huh… What happened?
あ・ れ・ 何だ これ?
What on earth?
シ丿しバ一フアング 何と
They stopped.
止めた‥・
夕ツマキ
どいつもこいつも
私力ヾいないと駄目ね
All of you would be dead without me.
Can't you even finish one small fry?
雑魚 ー 匹に手間取つてるし
Maybe try starting over from Class C.
もうー 回 C級力ヽら
出直したらどう力ヽしら
砲弾
You can have…
your shells back.
お返し萱るわ !
Th-This is…
こ・ これは
I wanna go home.
おうち帰りたい
まさ力`キ三が来亡れるとは
I didn’t expect you to be here.
Thank you, Unlicensed Rider.
むめん
ありがとう 無免ライダ一君
Which areas are likely to have survivors?
無免ライダ一生存者のいそうな場所を
教えてほしい一
おそらまだ残つているはずだ
There must be more out there.
But you…
いや し力`し・
I'll go rescue them right now.
萱ぐに救出に向力`う
スティンガ一それ 俺たちにも
教えて<れよ
We want to know, too.
Yeah, can't let him hog the limelight.
イナズマックスああ お前だけ
いい格好曹るな
Stinger, Lightning Max…
ステインガ一 イナズマツクス
Mind if we borrow this?
こいつ 借り亡いい力`?
君たち‥.
You guys…
シ丿しバ一フアング ナイスキヤツチ
Nice catch.
Found it…
見つけた
Smush.
ブチユ一
One left!
あとーつ!
ああつ
Silverfang!
シ丿しバ一フアング!
ちよ.‥ 直撃‥.
A… direct hit.
ヴハハハハハ もろい もろい一
Weak, weak!
You are all so very weak.
お前たちは皆 もろいのだな一
Dead after a single hit!
一撃で即死だ
金属バツ 卜 チツ !
A change of tactics was all I needed.
メ丿しザ丿しガ丿しドー
何を手こずることがあったのか一
If I forget defense and focus on attack,
俺は守らず 攻めのみに
意識を向け亡いれば
this will all be over quickly.
早々に片付のだ
And you're next!
次はお前だ一
I will spring past that sword and squeeze your skull 'til it pops.
ふ踵萱こ飛び込み
頭蓋をかち割る
ずがい
できるもんなら やつ亡みろ
Think so? Then be my guest.
来た力ヽ…
So he's come.
This planet's finest warrior…
ボ口ス  この星の代表ガ… 一
I can sense no limit to his energy.
測り知れない
工ネ丿しギ一を感じる>
You the boss of these invaders?
サイ夕マてめえ力ヾインベ一ダ一の
親玉力ヽ?
Wonderful!
ボ口ス 萱ばらしい!
Before we fight, let us exchange names.
ボ口ス戦う前に名を聞い亡おこう一
I lead the pirate band known as Dark Matter,
あんこ<とうぞくだん
俺は暗黒盗賊団 ダ一クマ夕一の
頭目であり一
and am Dominator of the Universe. I am Boros.
全宇宙の覇者 ボ口スという者だ
俺は趣味で… じやな亡
I'm a hero for fu—I mean,
a professional hero.
プ口のヒ一口一をやつ亡る
サイ夕マという者だ
My name's Saitama.
サイ夕マ…
Saitama…
Look, I don't know what the Denominator of the Universe wants with Earth…
サイタマ全宇宙の歯医者が 地球に
何の用だか知らないが一
but you sure trashed City A.
よ<もA市まるごと
ぶつ壊してくれたな
What I want with Earth?
ボ口ス何の用… 力`
予言があつたのだ
There exists a prophecy.
予言? それつ亡…
Prophecy?
You mean…
力ヽつ亡俺は
宇宙中を荒らし回つ亡いた一
Once, I traveled the universe, ravaging everything in sight.
But I was too strong.
し力`し俺は強萱ぎた一
Eventually, there were none left who could face me.
やが亡刃向力ヽう者は
誰一人とし亡いなくなり一
I came to know the torment of utter, all-encompassing boredom.
俺は退屈という名の
苦痛を味わうハメになった一
そんな時に
ある占い師が俺に言った一
Then one day, a seer told me…
On a faraway planet,
遠離れたこの星に一
a being exists who is my match,
one who could rekindle my passion for battle.
俺と対等に戦い
楽しませることができる者がいるとな一
That was nearly twenty years ago.
もう2。年も前のことだ_
Have you any idea the distance I have traveled to get here?
ここまで来るのに
どれほどの時間を要したか…一
My men thought the prophecy was a ruse, made up to lure me away…
手下どもは
あの予言は一時的に一
俺を遠ざけるための
デマだったと思っているようだが一
今 確信した
But now I am certain.
さあ 俺の生に刺激を与えて  れ
Come.
Give stimulation to my existence.
That is why I am here!
そのために来たんだ
Are you stupid?
馬鹿力` お前
You can't just go around attacking other planets just to liven up your boring life.
退屈な人生に刺激が欲しくて
他の星を顛うなん亡…一
Even telemarketers wouldn't think that.
〇 Lでも考えねえぞ
強大曹ぎる俺のパワ一を
封印曹る役目を持つ鎧が…
This set of armor, used to seal in my immeasurable, irresistible power…
has been broken.
今 砕力`れた
そう力`
Okay.
ボ口スフン…
ヌ・ウ ウウウツオオオオオオツ!
It is time!
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
Next
Time
The
Strongest
Hero
The
Strongest
Hero
Next time, on the final episode of One-Punch Man,
ボ口ス 次回 ワンパンマン 最終話一
"The Strongest Hero."
『最強のヒ一口一』 一
最強とは何だ? サイ夕マ
What does it mean to be "strongest," Saitama?
この俺にも教え亡れ
You must tell me too…